我们，是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
Steven: ♪ and if you think we can't, we'll ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
Pearl: ♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文！
and Steven!
在一起
翻译
零玖/presisco
校对
presisco
特效
压制
presisco
我们必须找到橄榄石
We need to track down Peridot.
我们找到了她的逃生舱
We found her pod.
我们知道她就在地球上
We know she's out there somewhere.
她来这里是因为有工作
She came to earth with a job to do,
而且很可能她还会试着完成
and odds are she's still gonna try to do it.
这是我将大家聚集到这里的原因
That's why I've gathered you here.
我以为是你为了能帮我把衣服都叠了
I thought it was so you could help me fold all this laundry.
啊，当然
Mm, that too.
你的家务轮的点子很快就失效了
The chore wheel idea you had fell apart fast.
不是我干的
Wasn't me.
我只是很乐于做这些事
I just really enjoy doing all of those things.
我们最好一起做
It's better if we do them together.
人类应该不穿衣服
Humans should just stop wearing clothes.
这会有趣很多
It'd be a lot funnier.
嘿！
Hey!
我是个有教养的半人，不谢！
I'm a civilified part-human, thank you very much.
衣服是必需品
Clothing is a must.
Hmm.
有点多啊
This is a lot.
我打赌如果红宝石和蓝宝石在的话
I bet this folding would go faster
叠起来一定会更快的
if Ruby and Sapphire were here.
我肯定她们会乐于见到你，史蒂文
I'm sure they'd be glad to see you, Steven,
我不会为了衣物解体的
but I am not unfusing for laundry.
嗷
Aw.
石榴，你不认为
Garnet, you don't think
橄榄石会来找我们吧？
Peridot would come looking for us, do you?
我们不是她的首要目标
We weren't her priority.
她被派来完成幼儿园的工作
She was sent here to do something in the kindergarten.
你觉得她还会尝试重启幼儿园？
Do you think she's still going to try to reactivate it?
Mm.
如果她重启成功了，注射器会重新工作的
If she gets it up and running, the injectors will turn back on.
注...射器？
In...Jectors?
那...那是什么？
W-what are those?
你已经看到过了
You've already seen them.
或者，你看到的是停用的
Well, you've seen them disabled.
如果橄榄石重新启动了注射器
If Peridot reactivates them,
它们会继续工作
they'll pick right up where they left off --
在地壳中种下宝石人
planting gems in the crust of the earth,
在那里他们会慢慢孵化
where they'll incubate
并从地表吸光生命
and suck the life right out of the ground.
我们不能让橄榄石重启这里的宝石人生产
We can't let Peridot restart gem production here.
如果失败了，整个星球会变成
If we do, the entire planet will become...
一片荒芜
Janked.
石榴！用词不错嘛！
Garnet!  That mouth!
不用担心。我们会阻止她
Don't worry. We'll stop her.
来吧，水晶战士
Come on, crystal gems.
马上
Coming.
呃。只要我们不用叠东西
Ugh. As long as we don't have to fold anything.
史蒂文
Steven.
来啊。显然也有你，对不对？
Come on. That means you, too, right?
毕竟你也是一个有教养的半宝石人
You're a civilified part-gem, too, after all.
石榴，你确定我们可以带上史蒂文？
Garnet, are you sure we should bring Steven?
这可能比较危险
This might be dangerous.
我们完全可以对付橄榄石
Peridot's got nothing we can't handle.
好吧，看起来没有启动的痕迹
Well, nothing looks activated.
实际上，没有东西看起来被修复过
In fact, it doesn't look like anything's budged
离上次来都这么长时间了
since the last time we were here.
你说的对
You're right.
但只是因为橄榄石还没来这里
But just because Peridot hasn't been here yet
不意味着她不会来
doesn't mean she won't come.
Hm.
我们来对场地做个仔细的检查
Let's do a thorough check of the perimeter.
这样，我们能监视任何将来进入的人
Mm-hmm. That way, we can monitor any future entry.
我觉得不错
Hm. Sounds good to me.
Mm, mmm, mm, mmm, mm, mmm,
mm, mmm, mm, mmm, mm, mmm, mm, mmm, mm...
记录日期 陆 贰 伍。我是橄榄石
Log date 652. This is Peridot.
更新状态——仍在被困在这可悲的星球上
Updating status -- still stuck on miserable planet.
融合实验的进展十分顺利
The fusion experiments are developing properly.
一少部分实验品已经提前孵化——
A few have even emerged early --
呀～哈！
eugggh! Huh!
其他人和你在一起吗？
Are the other ones with you?
当然。怎么会不呢？
Of course. Why not?
橄榄石！
Peridot!
她在那！——啊！
There she is!Aah!
你无处可逃！你已经被包围了！
There's nowhere to go! You're cornered!
嘿！我做不了这个！
Hey! I can't do that!
她也别想！
Neither can she!
哈！歪了！
Ha! Missed!
呃？
Huh?
啊啊啊！
Aaah!
啊啊啊啊！
Aaaah!
你觉得她受伤了吗？
Do you think she's hurt?!
并没有
Nope.
喔！鞭子变烫了！
Whoooooa! Hot whip!
你们这群水晶草包！来啊！互相伤害啊！
You crystal clods! Go ahead! Wreck this place!
看我在不在乎！我已经得到我要的了
See if I care. I already got what I needed.
回来！
Get back here!
我要给她点颜色瞧瞧！
I'm gonna bop her good!
我也要！
I'll help!
快点，石榴！
Hurry, Garnet!
如果橄榄石的任务是重启幼儿园，
If Peridot's mission was to reactivate the kindergarten,
注射器应该已经开启了
the injectors would be on.
看
Look.
它们并没有
They're not.
哦
Oh.
噢
我们来看看她到底在干什么
Let's see what she was actually doing.
在下面
Down here.
哦
Oh.
噢！
Oh!
你真是法师战士双修二合一啊！
You're brains and brawn -- the whole package.
多谢啦
Thank you. Ah.
是因为你是融合体吗？
Is it 'cause you're a fusion?
我总得有点不能说的秘密吧？
I have to keep some of my secrets.
噢，求求你了！我想知道！
Aw, please? I want to know!
你战士的能力来自红宝石
Is the strong part of you Ruby
法师的能力来自蓝宝石？
and the wise part of you Sapphire?
两个都有
It's all of both.
当两个宝石人结合时
When two gems combine,
会产生1+1>2的效果
it creates something greater than the sum of their parts.
这就是我如此炫酷掉渣天的原因
That's why I'm so great.
一直保持合体的感觉——
What's it like to stay fused all the --
whoa.
不知为何，这里感觉更瘆人
I don't know how, but this place is even creepier
相比我们上次来的时候
than the last time we were here.
对。显然有什么秘密
Yes. There's something going on.
电源没有恢复
The power's not on.
橄榄石当时在做什么？
What was Peridot doing?
看起来她从墙里把这些拉了出来
It looks like she pulled these out of the walls.
有事情不对
Something's strange.
石榴？
Garnet?
这里...不止我们吧？
Is there... Something in there?
啊！
Aah!
Whoa!
它们是什么？
What are they?
啊啊啊！
Aaah!
这是什么？
What is it?
看起来像两块宝石碎片拼在一起
It looks like two gem shards stuck together.
恶！
Ugh!
其它的都这样？
Is that what all these things are?
宝石...拼到一起？
Gems...Stuck together?
啊啊！
Aah!
石榴？
Garnet?
那是什么？
What was that?
啊！
Aah!
Mnh-mnh.
石榴？
Garnet?
呃...石榴！
Uh...Garnet!
我们该怎么办？
What do we do?!
啊！
Aah!
求求你！说句话啊！
Please! Talk to me!
呃～
Unh!
这些是被打碎的水晶战士
These were crystal gems shattered into pieces.
它们被埋在一起
They were buried together.
你怎么不动了？！
Why aren't you moving?!
它们被强制在一起
They were forced together.
它们被强制融合
They were forced to fuse.
这不对
This is wrong.
我-我-我对不起
I-I-I'm sorry.
不！不，石榴！
No! No, Garnet!
你快解体了！
You're coming undone!
石榴！
Garnet!
求求你！到底怎么了？！
Please! What's the matter?!
这一点也不像你！
This isn't like you!
我们做到了！
We did it!
石榴？
Garnet?
所以，这就是母世界看待融合体的态度
So, this is what homeworld thinks of fusion.
我们当时不可能知道她们会这么做
We couldn't have known they would do this.
她们原来在这里——所有我们找不到的人
This is where they've been -- all the ones we couldn't find.
她们一直都是这样
They've been here the whole time!
玫瑰不可能知道
Rose couldn't have known.
这是对叛乱的惩罚！这不是我们的错！
This was punishment for the rebellion! It's not our fault!
石榴！
Garnet!
史-史蒂文
S-Steven.
Yo.
我们回来了
We're back.
石榴，我们跟丢了橄榄石
Garnet, we lost Peridot.
她的手指对我们来说太快了
Her fingers were too fast for us.
呃...这些是什么？
Um... What are these things?
把它们放下！——什么？
Put them down! What?
我们需要将它们打回原形并用泡泡包起来
We need to poof and bubble all of them.
我们不能让任何物体离开这里
We can't let any escape.
哦。嘿，石榴
Oh. Hey, Garnet.
感觉怎么样？
How's it going?
还是很不好
Still damp.
哦。好吧——衣服
Oh. Right -- the clothes.
里面有毛巾
There are towels in there.
我们在这有水泵吗？
Do we even have plumbing up here?
你是怎么让洗衣机和甩干机工作的？
How do you get the washer and dryer to work?
魔法
Magic.
你还...好吗？
Are you...All right?
我希望你没看见那些
I wish you hadn't seen that.
这没什么
Aw, it's okay.
这很重要
It's not okay.
为-为什么？
W-why?
母世界所做的——
What homeworld did --
将消逝的宝石碎片
taking the shattered parts of fallen gems
拼接到一起
and combining them.
并没有得到那些宝石人的同意
Those gems weren't asked permission.
融合是自己的选择
Fusion is a choice.
那些宝石人没有选择的余地
Those gems weren't given a choice.
这不对！这不是融合！
It isn't right! It isn't fusion!
这是一种什么感受，作为一个融合体？
What's it like, being a fusion?
你融合过
You've fused.
我指，就像，无时无刻
I mean, like, all the time.
你们还记得原来的自己吗？
Do you forget who you used to be?
你只会忘记你曾经的孤独
You forget you were ever alone.
你看，当你融合时，你不会感觉像两个人
You know, when you fuse, you don't feel like two people.
你感觉像是一个个体
You feel like one being.
而且原来的你
And your old names might as well be names
感觉就像是左手和右手
for your left arm and your right.
当你解体时，你是消失了吗？
When you split up, is it like you disappear?
我的存在体现的是我的——
I embody my --
我指，红宝石和蓝宝石的爱
I mean, Ruby and Sapphire's love.
我永远存在于她们之中，即使我解体了
I'll always exist in them, even if I split apart.
但是那种爱的力量让我一直在一起
But the strength of that love keeps me together,
所以我作为石榴可以保持非常长的时间
so I can stay Garnet for a very long time.
这就是你如此出色的原因！——哦，不！
That's why you're so great.Oh, no!
不想拆开一对
Don't want to break up a pair.
是，你说的对
Yeah. You're right.
它们属于一起
They belong together.
如果我可以做到
♪ If I could begin to be
你对我期望的一半
♪ half of what you think of me
我愿意做任何事
♪ I could do about anything
我愿学会像你一样，去爱
♪ I could even learn how to love like you ♪